[{
    "question": "Today",
    "A": "Oggi",
    "B": "Dopo",
    "C": "Domani",
    "D": "Ieri",
    "correctAnswer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Good Morning",
    "A": "Buona giornata",
    "B": "Benvenuta",
    "C": "Buongiorno",
    "D": "Buonanotte",
    "correctAnswer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "How are you?",
    "A": "Come ti chiami?",
    "B": "Come stai?",
    "C": "Che cosa?",
    "D": "Cosa fai?",
    "correctAnswer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Spring, Summer, Autumn, Winter",
    "A": "primavera, inverno, autunno, estate",
    "B": "estate, primavera, autunno, inverno",
    "C": "primavera, estate, autunno, inverno",
    "D": "inverno, estate, autunno, primavera",
    "correctAnswer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Breakfast",
    "A": "colazione",
    "B": "cena",
    "C": "cibo",
    "D": "cucina",
    "correctAnswer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "I eat",
    "A": "Io mangiano",
    "B": "Io mangi",
    "C": "Io mangia",
    "D": "Io mangio",
    "correctAnswer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yesterday",
    "A": "Oggi",
    "B": "Dopo",
    "C": "Domani",
    "D": "Ieri",
    "correctAnswer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are you doing?",
    "A": "Come ti chiami?",
    "B": "Come stai?",
    "C": "Che cosa?",
    "D": "Cosa fai?",
    "correctAnswer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "600",
    "A": "cinquecento",
    "B": "seicento",
    "C": "cinquanta",
    "D": "seimila",
    "correctAnswer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Friday",
    "A": "lunedì",
    "B": "sabato",
    "C": "venerdi",
    "D": "martedì",
    "correctAnswer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Come ti ______",
    "A": "chiamo",
    "B": "chiami",
    "C": "chiama",
    "D": "sto",
    "correctAnswer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Io leggo ______",
    "A": "il portafoglio",
    "B": "il manzo",
    "C": "il topo",
    "D": "il libro",
    "correctAnswer": "D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Il topo",
    "A": "the mouse",
    "B": "yours",
    "C": "the bull",
    "D": "your",
    "correctAnswer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dici sul serio?",
    "A": "Are you serious?",
    "B": "Is that real?",
    "C": "Can you be serious?",
    "D": "Can you believe it?",
    "correctAnswer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dolce far niente",
    "A": "Sweet life",
    "B": "Sweet idleness",
    "C": "It is not sweet",
    "D": "It is sweet for me",
    "correctAnswer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Caldo",
    "A": "Hot",
    "B": "Cold",
    "C": "Ice",
    "D": "Can",
    "correctAnswer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sono stanco",
    "A": "I want to stay",
    "B": "I'm tired",
    "C": "They are watching",
    "D": "Stay here",
    "correctAnswer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Be careful",
    "A": "Stai buono",
    "B": "Stai zitto",
    "C": "Stai attento",
    "D": "Stai parlando",
    "correctAnswer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Be quiet",
    "A": "Stai buono",
    "B": "Stai zitto",
    "C": "Stai attento",
    "D": "Stai parlando",
    "correctAnswer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Be nice",
    "A": "Stai buono",
    "B": "Stai zitto",
    "C": "Stai attento",
    "D": "Stai parlando",
    "correctAnswer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tu ____ la torta",
    "A": "mangi",
    "B": "leggi",
    "C": "bevi",
    "D": "scrivi",
    "correctAnswer": "A"
  },
  {
    "question": "La torta ha un ____ dolce",
    "A": "fame",
    "B": "gusto",
    "C": "rosso",
    "D": "colore",
    "correctAnswer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ a Wroclaw",
    "A": "Sono",
    "B": "Chiamo",
    "C": "Abito",
    "D": "Ho",
    "correctAnswer": "C"
  },
  {
    "question": "La dolce vita",
    "A": "Sweet drink",
    "B": "Sweet life",
    "C": "Sweet dream",
    "D": "Sweet home",
    "correctAnswer": "B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Terra nova",
    "A": "New me",
    "B": "Now something new",
    "C": "New beginning",
    "D": "New earth",
    "correctAnswer": "D"
  }
]